{
    "subject": "resource/Thunderbolt_and_Lightfoot",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Michael_Cimino",
    "human_readable": "The director of Thunderbolt and Lightfoot is Michael Cimino.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9393523335456848,
            "question": "Name the director of the movie Thunderbolt and Lightfoot."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8845723867416382,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.863551914691925,
            "question": "What is the name of the director of Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8400809168815613,
            "question": "Is Michael Cimino a film director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8367905020713806,
            "question": "Tell me about the director of Thunderbolt and Lightfoot."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8050621151924133,
            "question": "What is Michael Cimino known for directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7499699592590332,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie directed by Michael Cimino?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6926667094230652,
            "question": "Michael Cimino directed which popular film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.635812520980835,
            "question": "Which movie is associated with Michael Cimino?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5612534284591675,
            "question": "What film did Michael Cimino direct?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of Thunderbolt and Lightfoot is Michael Cimino.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3169_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which movie is associated with Michael Cimino?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3169_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Cimino directed which popular film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3169_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the movie directed by Michael Cimino?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3169_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3169_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3169_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3169_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3169_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3169_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3169_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3169_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3169_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3169_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3169_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Michael Cimino made his directorial debut with 1974\u2019s Thunderbolt And Lightfoot,\" which supports the statement that Michael Cimino was the director of Thunderbolt and Lightfoot."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}